{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The M41 Walker Bulldog remains in service in some countries to this day.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science: Mathematics",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The proof for the Chinese Remainder Theorem used in Number Theory was NOT developed by its first publisher, Sun Tzu.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Mythology",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "History",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Abraham Lincoln was the first U.S. President to be born outside the borders of the thirteen original states. ",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Vehicles",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Bugatti was an Italian car manufacturer.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]
}